Do you think people will return to Kfar Aza?
It will take time.
I don't know how many will be back.
Not all of them will be back.
I think that my daughter will not be back,
and I have nothing to tell her,
and I will not try to to convince her.
because it's not...
I can not.
I can not tell her:
"I want you to live with me here in Kfar Aza".
Because she's afraid.
She hasn't been here since the October 7th.
Since the day when when we were together,
when went out,
she wasn't in her own house.
a child, the little one, Rif,
he doesn't know his house,
he has never been there.
So, most of the people, I believe, will come back.
It will take time, but most of them will be back.
But a big part of us will not be back.